[Music]
[Música]
Well let's see family about the mafia
bueno a ver familia lo de mafia
there are a lot of people who are asking me
hay mucha gente que me está preguntando
about the cntv mafia issue we already
por el tema de mafia cntv ya hemos
talked about it here the other day okay what's
hablado de ello aquí el otro día vale
going on with mafia let's
qué es lo que está pasando con mafia
see my magic the most faithful one I don't like him he
a ver a mi magia a mí más fiel no me cae
never had a
bien nunca me haber tuvo un trato
pretty cordial relationship with him for a few
bastante cordial con él durante unos
years but
años pero
the truth is he started attacking me
la verdad empezó a atacarme
for free when I got into a fight with
gratuitamente cuando yo me peleé con
drones and look how you don't have to act like
drones y fíjate como no tienes que ir de
anyone's poodle you don't have to act like
de caniche de nadie no tienes que ir de
anyone's biting poodle because with
caniche mordedor de nadie porque a
your finances that's how things are
financias de tu como son las cosas que
after a year the waters calm down
al cabo de un año se calman las aguas
hard and I we
duros y yo
call them on the phone through
los llamamos por teléfono a través de
a third person we give each other a couple of
una tercera persona nos damos un par de
kisses we forgive each other for posting a tweet
besito nos perdonamos el poner un tweet
apologizing for what hurt me what he
disculpándose por lo que a mí me dolió
said about my wife I
qué fue lo que dijo de mi mujer yo le
took down some videos he took them all down
quité unos vídeos él quitó todos
we had some talks eating we didn't give them
hicimos unas charlas que comiendo nos
[ __ ] and even for example and you got in the
los nepe y hasta ejemplo y tú te metiste
middle you came out splashed
por medio saliste salpicado
for trying to get the other guy to give you two
por intentar que el otro te diera dos
slaps  in the back
palmas en la espalda
when there are two adults and
cuando haya dos personas adultas y sobre
especially very adult
todo muy adulta
octogenarians as we are tough and I don't
octogenaria como somos duros y yo no nos
involve us and really for your pair [ __ ] do not
metas y de verdad por su par pollas no
involve yourselves really
os metáis de verdad
and sincerely well I did a debate
y sinceramente pues yo hice un debate
with mafia in which it turned out very badly I do not have it
con mafia en el que quedó muy mal no lo
uploaded because I
tengo subido porque me
missed an age restriction
me saltó una restricción de edad
when I get an
cuando a mí me sale una restricción de
age restriction on a YouTube video as I do not
edad en un vídeo de youtube como no
want
quiero ningún
any video with an age restriction on
ningún vídeo con restricción de edad en
my channel I delete it because I delete it well I delete it
mi canal lo borro porque lo borro pues
because I think that in some
lo borro porque creo que eso de alguna
way marks my channel or harms it or
manera marca mi canal o lo perjudica o
something like that so
algo por el estilo entonces
why don't I summarize it because it is already the
por qué no lo resumo porque ya es el
glass like a year around there and I am not going to
vaso como al año por ahí y no lo voy a
summarize it because I was already talking to two and
resumir porque ya me hablaba con dos y
the debate in part well it was
el debate en parte pues era
throwing a drone box so it
tirándole cajita drone entonces pues
would be like attacking 2 what is happening
sería como atacar a 2 qué es lo que pasa
because in this debate well I put this
porque en este debate bueno le metí este
debate it was also things that I am not going to
debate fue además cosas que no os voy a
tell you who public but you do not have
decir quién público pero tú no tienes
are absolutely these this debate was
son absolutamente estas este debate fue
absolutely unprepared or rather it was out of the blue
absolutamente sin preparar o sea fue de
he was putting
buenas a primeras él me estaba poniendo
something in your and I was not greedy it was and it arose
algo en tu y no me goloso fue y surgió
automatically  the two months but the two
automáticamente los dos mes pero los dos
I was tremendously reviewing it the
me tremendamente lo estuve repasando el
other day and well, like I'm not going to
otro día y bueno en plan no lo voy a
summarize it because it's attacking two and drone
resumir porque es atacar a dos y drone
more clearly many things in which I
más claro muchas cosas en las que yo
bring kalfin things but above all the
traigo kalfin cosas pero sobre todo el
end man can you send me the title of
final tío me puedes mandar el título de
forced journalist of course I say I don't
periodista forzado por supuesto digo no
have it here at hand but yes let me
lo tengo aquí a la mano pero sí déjame
see if I have a copy here
ver si tengo aquí alguna copia
directory but it says and selling they
directorio pero dice y vendiendo me
just sent me the link
acaban de mandar el link
cell professional license of
cel cédula profesional
course that
claro ese punto
professional point of this here does not appear as a
profesional de esto aquí no figura como
journalism graduate
licenciado en periodismo
[Laughter]
[Risas]
the question
la pregunta
better I show you the type
mejor te enseño la el tipo
but
pero
on the government website
en la web del gobierno
when you obviously have a degree
cuando tú tienes obviamente un título
that is risky and when you carry out cases
que es riesgoso y cuando llevas casos
that are complicated as if it were from the
que son complicados como si fuera del
FBI or something ajam crypts
fbi o algo ajam criptas
then here the government protects you
entonces aquí el gobierno te protege
so long big and here it's already gone I mean
hasta luego grande y aquí ya se piró o
the debate is a spectacle the
sea el debate es un espectáculo el
debate a spectacle because I put
debate un espectáculo porque le meto
houses here very low-class I for my
casas acá muy barriobajeros yo para mi
taste the truth this was already due to a dismissal
gusto la verdad esto hace ya por un cese
three years ago I think this was after
hace tres años creo que esto fue después
the pandemic but it wasn't that long ago
de la pandemia pero tampoco hace tanto
but it is true that now with the
pero sí que es verdad que ahora con el
passage  over the years I don't know if it's because I've
paso de los años no sé si porque me he
gotten older not to look at
vuelto más más mayor no mirar a salir
people going out because in family disputes
gente porque en a disputar familiar
now people have appeared on YouTube
aparece ahora salió gente en youtube
searching for his name
buscando su nombre
in the registry of these cells in
en el registro de las células estas de
Mexico and so on and he doesn't appear he doesn't appear
méjico y demás y no aparece no aparece
I don't know if this man is a journalist or
yo no sé si este hombre es periodista o
not but I really think he's a very
no pero yo realmente pienso que es muy
bad person. From the conversation and the
mala persona yo por la charla y las
things that happened to me with him I think he
cosas que me pasaron con él yo pienso
's a very bad person. A very bad
que es muy mala persona sea muy mala
person.
persona
The cases when he defends who he
los casos cuando defiende con quién se
gets close to, you know, it's like I do
arrima saber sea en plan
n't like him he's a person that the further
no me gusta es una persona que cuanto
away the better
más lejos mejor
sincerely he's a person but to
sinceramente es una persona pero para
prepare
preparar
and that's what I'm telling you if in the debate he
y es lo que os digo si en el debate lo
brutally tames him for my taste of
dome brutalmente para mi gusto de
schedules for my taste today well
horarios para mi gusto a día de hoy pues
with the passing of the years I don't know if I've
con el paso de los años no sé si me ha
gotten older and I want more
vuelto más viejo y quiero más
peace and quiet or whatever in which
tranquilidad o lo que sea en el que
well now I would do it differently I would
bueno ahora yo lo haría de otra manera
eat it with potatoes anyway
me lo comería igualmente con patatas
but I would do it more calmly not yelling
pero lo haría con más calma no chillando
taking the debate on the other side no but
llevando el debate por otro lado no pero
well these are things these are times that each
bueno son cosas de son épocas que cada
one has in life no I have gone through that
uno tienen la vida no yo he pasado ese
a chav from the neighborhood on YouTube when I
un cani del barrio en youtube cuando
started in that  2016 15 2016 2017 2018
empecé en eso de 2016 15 2016 2017 2018
2019 still regling in the vocabulary
2019 todavía regling en el vocabulario
many times and as it has gone
muchas veces y ya conforme ha ido
by measured correcting today one
pasando por medido corrigiendo hoy uno
gets older one becomes very old apart I have
se hace mayor se hace bien vejete aparte
built myself of we can say
me he construido de podemos decir
but simply I was completely right
pero simplemente tenía yo toda la razón
in everything that in everything I say in
en todo lo que en todo lo que digo en
everything I talk or rather I took it but
todo lo que hablo o sea me lo cogí pero
it can really rich do not ask me
me lo puede bien rico no me preguntáis
about what has happened to see there are many
sobre lo que ha pasado a ver hay mucha
people rather making it viral to me
gente más bien estar haciendo viral a mí
no to me he does not seem like a good person
no a mí no me parece una buena persona
I do not want
yo no quiero
absolutely anything to do with him many
absolutamente nada con él muchos me
tell me that the wave and not to see I do not have
decir que la onda y no ver no tengo
time right now for a ninth thousand
tiempo ahora mismo para un noveno mil
938 and two more it was useless or rather
938 y de dos más no servía de nada o sea
the public millions of the public of him
el público millones del público de él
and this is like others that we have commented on
y esto es como otros que hemos comentado
on the channel but from other countries whoever does
en el canal pero de otros países el que
not want to see things, do not see them to
no quiera ver las cosas que no las vea a
me what has done regarding the Bani case
mí lo que ha hecho respecto al caso de
I sincerely have been watching the
yo sinceramente he estado viendo los
videos this afternoon to be able to give an opinion and I
vídeos esta tarde para poder opinar y yo
personally have not seen them one hundred
personalmente no los he visto al cien
percent okay not them  I have seen one hundred
por cien vale no los he visto al cien
percent but in what he has done
por cien pero en lo que ha hecho
regarding the Bani case
referente al caso de baní
in other cases and I have seen some
en otros casos y que visto algunas de
other filth but regarding the
otras guarrada pero referente al caso de
Bani case in the videos that I have seen I have
bani en los vídeos que yo he visto
not seen anything bad okay today I have earned
no he visto nada malo vale hoy he ganado
a lot of money I do not know what he has earned what he
mucho dinero no sé qué ha ganado lo que
has generated
ha generado
already but it is that he has earned
ya pero es que ha ganado dinero en
more money on YouTube he has earned more money on Facebook what he
youtube más dinero en facebook ha ganado
has generated I
lo que ha generado
mean, I have this opinion of this
o sea yo esta opinión de esté moralismo
cheap moralism and complacency we have to get
barato y bienquedismo tenemos que ir
used to the fact that YouTube and other
acostumbrando una que youtube y otro
media outlets okay then the
medio de comunicación vale entonces la
television reports on cases not
tele informa de los casos no de casos
delicate cases like this as if it were a
delicados como éste como si fuera un
case like Marta del Castillo's as
caso como el de marta del castillo como
if it were a case like okay and
si fuera un caso como el de vale y yo
here what I have seen correct myself if I am
aquí lo que he visto corregirme si me
wrong is that yes there are a lot of videos a
equivoco es que sí que son muchos vídeos
lot of views but it is that it is the
muchas visitas pero es que son las
views that it generates in other words a case that
visitas que genera o sea un caso que a
people have been interested in and if he has
la gente le ha interesado y si él ha
been covering the news even
estado cubriendo la noticia incluso que
the one who has gone to the scene of the
el que se ha desplazado al lugar de los
events was already there pending besides there
hechos ya estaba allí pendiente además
are many places where there are
hay muchos sitios en los que
many cases where he gives the
hay muchos casos los que el da la
news before the television itself
noticia antes que la propia televisión
okay then bad bad bad I do not see it
vale entonces mal mal mal no lo veo
because because he hasn't disrespected her
porque porque no ha faltado al respeto
then the girl's father also wanted to
luego el padre de la chica también le ha
give him an interview he has given two or three
dar entrevista que él ha dado dos o tres
interviews so even though
entrevistas entonces yo a pesar de que a
he doesn't seem like a person to me for a
mí él no me parece una persona desde
long time because I know him and I
hace mucho tiempo porque yo lo conozco y
know many other cases of other types
sé otros muchos más casos de otro tipo
of content that he has made where he has
de contenido que ha hecho donde ha
defamed you [ __ ] okay but I don't see any slight or bad thing about the
difamado que te cagas vale pero yo los
videos that he reviews for this just because he has
vídeos que repasa por esto por el simple
profited maybe
hecho de que se haya lucrado no le veo
in some video okay praise
en algún vídeo vale loa
as if he has played with morbidity okay
como que ha jugado con el morbo vale yo
for example today on the main channel I
por ejemplo hoy en el canal principal he
made a video
hecho un vídeo
in which I dealt with the Bani case to
en el que trató el caso de bani para
give him information on the subject it has already
darle para informar sobre el tema ya ha
gone viral okay let's move on
pasado la viralidad vale
from the virality of the moment he
ya pasar de la viralidad del momento me
informs me well on the subject places he
informa bien con el tema lugares me
helps me with the script man an
ayuda con el guión macho un guión
incredible script an incredible compilation and
increíble una recopilación increíble y
with I don't see it
con yo no lo veo
here and I have uploaded a video to the main channel today
aquí y he subido hoy un vídeo al canal
on the subject
principal sobre el tema
nothing happens there is nothing wrong with the
no pasa nada no tiene nada de malo el
subject the problem is that I don't know if he has
tema el problema es que no sé si lo ha
done it in any of his videos because as I
hecho en alguno de sus vídeos porque ya
tell you I have not been able to see
os digo que tampoco me he podido ver hoy
all the  direct the problem is that in
todos los directos el problema es que en
all these videos he has played with
todos estos vídeos haya jugado con el
morbidity at some point,
morbo en algún momento
whether it's water with the morbidity he has become
ya sea agua con el morbo se ha puesto a
sensationalist he has taken out
ser amarillismo ha sacado vídeo
unnecessary videos to profit
innecesario por lucrarse
unnecessarily okay like for example
innecesariamente vale como por ejemplo
when we have criticized here that a
cuando hemos criticado aquí que una
person about a famous person dying takes
persona de que se muera un famoso te
out 30 videos that day congress a little
saque 30 vídeos ese día congreso un poco
exaggerated
exagerado
and understand the difference the point is not whether it is
y entender la diferencia el punto no es
right or wrong
que esté bien o mal
and profit or make money from a
y lucrarse o sacar dinero de que de un
topic like this if you are a
tema así si eres un medio de
media outlet and you have a channel on
comunicación y tienes un canal en
youtube you are doing it without
youtube está haciéndolo sin faltar al
disrespect informing and your thing like for
respeto informando y tu rollo como por
example the salsa of frnkel or victorio
ejemplo el salsa de fránkel o victorio
who also take out many videos this
que también sacan muchos vídeos este
topic many visits there is nothing wrong with the
tema muchas visitas no tiene de malo el
point is that you for example thing a famous person dies
tema es que tú por ejemplo cosa se muere
a famous person dies and out of take 30 videos
se muere un famoso y de saque 30 vídeos
oh look at the tweet that the sister has posted
ay mira el tweet que ha puesto la
look at this or even with
hermana a mirar esto o incluso con
false headlines and false things that I don't
titulares falsos y cosas falsas que no
know if he has done it okay I don't know if because
sé si lo ha hecho vale no sé si porque
for example here there are many videos that
por ejemplo aquí hay muchos vídeos que
I have not seen okay I don't know if I have done it
yo no he visto vale no sé si lo he hecho
how is the old 40 l it smells good good
cómo está el viejo de 40 l huele bien
good  Thank you very much,
bien bien muchas gracias
the reason for the case of the bank's father
el motivo el caso del padre de the bank
and her giving many interviews, I think that
y la da muchas entrevistas yo creo que
when vanilla's father agreed to
cuando el padre de vanilla ha consentido
the interviews it wasn't that
las entrevistas no habrá sido tan
bad, the content there was no lack of
tan malo el contenido no habrá falta de
respect, okay, then they have come out
respeto vale luego sí que han salido
here in a tweet, let's
aquí en un tuit
say because it has gone viral in
que digamos porque se ha hecho viral en
Mexico, Mari's father said that
méxico el padre de mari dijo que más
TV has profited from the death of his
bien tv ha lucrado con la muerte de su
daughter which is true and you know what
hija lo cual es cierto y saben que hizo
Fabian de Ardido did in a live broadcast he said to
fabián de ardido en un en vivo dijo a
Mario Escobar that he forgot his daughter at
mario escobar se le olvidó su hija a las
5 in the morning that's why what happened to him happened to him, in other
5 de mañana por eso le sucedió lo que le
words, de Bani's father
sucedió o sea el padre de de baní
finds out that Fabian has made an
se entera de que fabián ha sacado un
incredible amount of money with the videos and with
dineral increíble con los vídeos y con
the content, okay,
el contenido vale
and he decides to create a channel on YouTube
y decide crearse el un canal en youtube
and be the one who informs
y ser el que informa
before people profit
antes de que la gente se lucre
and Fabian doesn't like this, he doesn't
y esto a fabián pues no le gusta no le
like that all of a sudden this man takes the
gusta que de repente este señor se lleve
piece of cake that
el el trozo de pastel que se estaba
he was taking and then he starts saying
llevando él y entonces empieza a decir
very ugly things about de
cosas muy feas sobre el padre de de
Banif's father and this is where I see the worst,
banif y aquí es donde yo veo lo peor
okay, here where I see  The worst thing is, I insist,
vale aquí donde yo veo lo peor insisto
I want to make it clear, I've seen
quiero dejarlo claro yo he visto
tons of how fast
montones de a qué velocidad es que ha
Fabian has done something in many
hecho fabián en muchos algo en muchos
years, I know what he's done and he's
años que se lo que él ha hecho y ha
done terrible things. If one day I
hecho cosas terribles si algún día le
make him a wine, see flip you'll do it, but in
hago un vino ver flip haréis pero de
fact, gay, don't see it to throw your hands up in
hecho gay no ver para echar las manos a
the air, okay, but now I don't have
la cabeza vale pero ahora no tengo
time for that, okay,
tiempo para eso vale
the issue if he treats her with respect, he does
yo el tema si la trata con respeto
n't see any problem, for example, I
no le ve ningún problema yo por ejemplo
saw the day that the girl who
he visto el día que aparece la chica que
is informing him appears, even before the
le está informando antes incluso que los
media, besides, apparently the media
medios además por lo visto los medios
there in Mexico
allí de mexico
and the authorities don't have much
y las autoridades no tienen mucha
confidence in the people, it's not worth it,
confianza para el pueblo no vale no pasa
nothing's happening, what I've seen is warri Ximo, the
nada lo que yo he visto warri ximo es el
attack he's been making on
ataque que le está haciendo al padre de
Mari's father since he became the man,
mari desde que se ha hecho el hombre
channel,
canal
you know, very handsome, I don't know if he's playing with
sabes guapísimo ya no sé si habrá jugado
morbidity, if he's made up
en el morbo si se habrá inventado
news, I don't know if that's true,
noticias no lo sé si es así
put it in the comments box,
me lo ponéis en la caja de comentarios
okay, what I'm telling you is that the little
vale yo lo que os digo es que lo poco
that I've seen, I haven't seen anything bad in
que yo he visto no he visto nada malo en
the videos, I've told him that he's
los vídeos yo le he dicho que él anda
also more or less giving the
además en más o menos está dando la
information that the
información que se está dando en las
authorities are giving, well  for example at the
autoridades pues por ejemplo al
beginning when he talks about the motel I think
principio cuando habla del motel
it's in this video
creo que es en este vídeo
when he talks about the motel cameras he
él cuando habla de las cámaras del motel
says the same thing that the authorities say at the beginning,
dice lo mismo que dice al principio las
that the cameras
autoridades que las cámaras solamente
are only monitoring and that they don't record,
están monitoreando y que no graban
so I don't know, then I see him walking
entonces no se luego lo veo que se pasea
around the area and finding more cameras
por la zona y encuentra más cámaras
where the trailers are, I don't see him, leaving
donde los tráiler no lo veo dejando a un
aside other things that I have seen in
lado que otras cosas que yo he conocido
previous years in his content that he has
años anteriores en su contenido que ha
saved with many people he has done
hecho guardada con mucha gente ha hecho
terrible things in this specific case
cosas terribles en este caso en concreto
I have not seen anything bad the only thing that I
yo no he visto nada malo lo único que yo
do see from relatives is that he disappears
sí veo de familiares que él desaparece
from YouTube and only appears when there are
de youtube y solamente aparece cuando
cases like that for example the other day
hay casos así por ejemplo el otro día me
you told me to finish the man thing and
dijisteis ya terminar lo de the man y
now there's the case of the other girl who was
ahora está el caso de la otra niña que
found dead Yolanda Martinez and
han encontrado muerta yolanda martínez y
now he's going to get into a mess with that pim pim
ahora se va a liar con ese tema pim pim
pim issue and look apparently this issue
pim y mira por lo visto así este tema no
is not as viral from what I see it's the
es igual de viral por lo que veo es lo
only thing that I see
único que yo veo
that disappears from YouTube in fact let's go
que desaparece de youtube de hecho vamos
to the numbers I refer to him he disappears from
a las cifras me remito él desaparece de
YouTube and every time there is a case like that he kind of
youtube y cada vez que hay un caso así
resembles the line
medio que vuelve a parecerse a la línea
the guy has had before  of these 600
el tío tiene tenía antes de estos 600
thousand monthly visits
mil visitas mensuales
and starting with dany boon
y a partir de lo de dany boon
35 million visits I
35 millones de visitas
think that's 42 million visits
creo que son 42 millones de visitas las
that were obtained in the last month on youtube
que se sacan el último mes en youtube
plus what has had a twist that has
más lo que ha tenido un twist que ha
had tens of thousands of viewers
tenido decenas de miles de espectadores
you know facebook
you know facebook
has taken out we are going to take out a lot of money but
ha sacado vamos a sacar un dineral pero
well up to here what has generated we are not
bueno hasta acá lo que ha generado ya no
going to get into a
nos vamos a poner tampoco en plan
moralistic plan of he would have been a better person if he
moralista de sería mejor persona si
had taken out three thousand euros instead of a
hubiera sacado tres mil euros en vez de
hundred thousand he
cien mil
has taken out what he has generated
ha sacado lo que ha generado
chacho ricos and lazio ricos but to take out
chacho ricos y lazio ricos pero a sacar
what has generated okay
lo que ha generado vale
listen that he played with the morbidity that he
oye que haya jugado con el morbo que
has given false news that he has
haya dado noticia falsa que haya mal
misinformed I do not ignore it because I do not
informado no lo desconozco porque no lo
know if he has done it well it seems wrong to me
sé si lo ha hecho pues me parece mal yo
what I do see as terrible is the attack that he
lo que sí veo terrible es el ataque que
is making on this man from what you come out
le está haciendo a este hombre a partir
now I do not give a damn I am there
que ahora sales me vale madre estoy ahí
for you
por ti
when you go like
cuando vas a
that I do not give a damn truck but I am going for
así me valen [__] camión pero voy por
you they are going to say that I am ridiculous I do not
ti van a decir que soy una ridícula no
know that the girl I do not give a damn
sé que la chica me vale madre
passed by you
pasó por ti
and you shut up
y te callas
over there someone said it was 4 am and
por ahí alguien dijo eran las 4 am y
changed the  schedule just like what
cambió el horario de igual manera que
the [ __ ] was doing a school for
chingados estaba haciendo una escuela de
18 year olds at 4 in the morning he
18 años a las 4 de las [__] mañana
basically starts blaming the father for
se pone básicamente a culpar al padre de
what happened to the girl dude I mean it's
lo que le pasó a la niña tío o sea es
terrible it's terrible
terrible es terrible
this other one look how he advertises look look at
este otro mira como publicita mira mira
this one how he advertises the interview he
este como publicita la entrevista que le
did with mafia okay because mafia
hizo a mafia vale porque mafia lo han
invited him to this thanks to manny's case
invitado a esto gracias al caso de manny
look how he advertises it dude everything about the
mira como lo publicita tío todo sobre el
beni case and the truth is that it's
caso de de beni y la verdad es que está
pretty pretty good I'll leave the link
bastante bastante bueno les dejo el link
here the truth is that it's pretty
por acá la verdad es que está bastante
pretty good as if it were gossip
bastante bueno como si fuera un chisme
sites who knows what night that makes you profit from the
sitos a saber qué noche que te lucre del
subject okay he's doing a job he's
tema vale está haciendo un trabajo está
informing hey if you have to earn the
informando oye si tienes que ganar el
money that corresponds to 40 million
dinero que corresponda a 40 millones de
visits for what you earn you are not a better or
visitas por lo ganas no eres mejor o
worse person if he earns 100 thousand euros to
peor persona si gana 100 mil euros a
reach 3000 he's not informing you're
llegar a 3000 no está informando estás
doing a job you earn it but
haciendo un trabajo lo ganas pero me
these ways don't seem right to me the truth okay
estás formas no me parece la verdad vale
look at these
mirar estos
gentlemen they
señores
forgot their daughter at 5 in the
se le olvidó su hija a las 5 de la
morning at 18 years old not to me
mañana a sus 18 años a mí no
If I had been on the phone, I blame the father, I blame the father for not picking up the girl's phone at that time. Well, in such a way, the girl was not the one who called, the one who called the father, the girl did not call the father at any time, it
niña no llamó al padre en ningún momento
was her friends and they would not have had
fueron las amigas y tampoco les hubiera
time unfortunately, they could have
dado tiempo por desgracia haber evitado
probably avoided what happened but in such a
seguramente lo que pasó pero de tal
way that she tells you this now
manera es que esto te lo dice ahora
because she has become frustrated because the father
porque se ha frustrado porque el padre
is taking a piece of the cake from her
le está quitando un trozo del pastel
but while she was interviewing
pero mientras que estaba entrevistando
the father
al padre
and all this, I don't know if it has been a month and a
y todos estos no sé si ha sido un mes y
half or two months that she has been talking
medio o dos meses que ha estado hablando
about the case on you know, on Facebook and
sobre el caso en you know en facebook y
in your separate report, she hasn't said anything in fact,
en tu aparte no ha dicho nada de hecho
man, man,
hombre tío
man, and there is a screenshot that
hombre tío y hay aquí una captura que
people put up, look at these shots, I
pone la gente mira estos tiros
mean, look
o sea fijaros
how she gets on the day she finds the
como se pone el día que encuentra el
father and has to identify
padre y tiene que reconocer el cuerpo de
his daughter's body, she
su hija
knew that it was outside the motel that
sabía que estaba afuera del motel que
was all
estaba todo
cordoned off by the police,
acordonado por la policía
sending jokes to the father, uncle
mandándoles guasas al padre tío
stooges, let me give you the details, various, confirms,
stooges a déjeme detalle varios confirma
studies me or has insistently and
me estudia o nos ha insistentemente sin
tactlessly
ningún tacto
looked at the messages that the father sent her,
míralo los mensajes que le mandaba el
God, we
padre dios
are talking about  that they have
estamos hablando de que se han
found your daughter dead
encontrado a tu hija muerta
assume a terrible video man I saw the
asume un vídeo terrible tío yo visto el
video and the truth is I'm not going to react
vídeo y la verdad no lo voy a reaccionar
but the bid is terrible this guy
pero el bid es terrible este vale
in the video has the balls to
en el vídeo tiene los santos huevos de
say I withdraw support from now on
decir yo retiro a partir de ahora el
I withdraw support
yo retiro el apoyo
for this father because he is stuck
a este padre porque está con pinchado
with the authorities I made the video
con la con las autoridades yo el vídeo
on the main channel I base it
he hecho en el canal principal me baso
on official information from the
en la información oficial en la de las
authorities because that is really the one that
autoridades porque es que la realmente
seems more logical to me
en la que me parece que tiene más lógica
but it says in the video I am going to take down all
pero dice en el vídeo voy a bajar todos
the videos that I have made about the Bani case he
los vídeos que he hecho sobre el caso de
has not removed them they
no los ha quitado
removed it and one
la quitaron y uno
has not removed anything they
no ha quitado nada
are still generating money for him
le están generando pasta todavía
'don mario' strong what he is
'don mario' fuerte lo que está
declaring but what happened
declarando pero qué fue lo que sucedió
with this youtuber that at some point
con este youtuber que en algún momento
we saw images where you tell him
vimos imágenes donde usted le dice
you arrived late
llegaste tarde
and now we understand that there has been
y ahora entendemos que ha habido por ahí
some friction because they are
alguna fricción porque le están
using the Bani case to be able to
utilizando el caso de de bani para poder
make what was happening well he told
hacer que estaba sucediendo pues él dijo
the truth I have nothing against or
la verdad yo no tengo nada en contra ni
in favor of him he is doing
a favor de él él está haciendo entre
his job so to speak I am a teacher I have
comillas su trabajo yo soy maestro tengo
a salary I do not know if that is  dedicate
un sueldo yo no sé si que eso se dedique
and if you do this it's good that God
y si esto lo hace es bueno que dios lo
bless you. I have no problem
bendiga yo no tengo ningún problema al
opening my YouTube channel to
abrir yo mi canal de youtube para
inform people
informar a la gente
about the information that I have there so that
sobre la información que tengo yo ahí es
the information is not diverted so
para que no se desvíe la información
that no one can handle the information
para que nadie puede con la información
of mystery regarding much of everything that
de misterio respecto mucho todo lo que
others always host or several you cannot
los demás siempre alojen o varios no se
profit from the pain of using your
puede lucrar con el dolor de uso de tu
wife and the pain of a death you
mujer y el dolor de una muerte no se
cannot look for followers with this type of
puede buscar followers con este tipo de
things gentlemen this has to
cosas señores de eso se tiene que
end because let's see if you are not
terminar por a ver si tú no estás
doing to inform because you have
haciendo para informar porque tú tienes
an active channel and you within your
un canal activo y tú dentro de tu
content you
contenido
are doing between all the content
estás haciendo entre todo el contenido
add information about that but we
añade información de eso pero es que
have a man who only
tenemos a un señor que no que únicamente
appears with these cases to take advantage of
aparece con estos casos para aprovechar
the vitality of these cases that is the
la vitalidad de estos casos ese es el
problem that I see
problema que yo le veo
if you have a channel that listens today he touches on
si tú tienes un canal que oye hoy toca
this subject grandpa today he is very deaf in
este tema abuelo hoy está muy sordo en
the mafia video he said that he was going to download
el vídeo de mafia decía que iba a bajar
all the videos where he promoted
todos los vídeos donde le daba promoción
the channel of the father of the band and not the
al canal del papá de the band y no los
lives of bani a disgusting the truth
vidas de de bani un asqueroso la verdad
a greeting javi always with you
un saludo javi siempre contigo te
we love you if you already go to  an audiologist
queremos si ya ve a un audiólogo
then
entonces
who is the one who worked, I mean, he has
entonces cuál es el trabajado
only downloaded whoever he
o sea solamente ha bajado
is, he has only downloaded the video
el que sea solamente ha bajado el vídeo
in which he says the bank's dad and he already has a
en el que dice el papá de the bank y ya
channel on YouTube
tiene canal en youtube
it's the only video he works on today your deaf guy
es el único vídeo trabaja hoy tu sordo
today then and even so they do
hoy entonces y aún así
n't appear in negative here yet
no le aparecen en negativo aquí todavía
the visits or rather look at what is
las visitas o sea fíjate tú lo que está
generating still
generando todavía
get to work don't take these
pónganse a trabajar no agarrar estas
causes to look for a job for your
causas para buscar una chamba para tus
vices but we understand that you had
vicios pero entendemos que tú le habías
asked him to go so that he
pedido a él que fuera para que él se
realizes and will verify when
diera cuenta y constatará cuando fue
this was planted because that would have been
esto sembrado porque eso hubiese sido
important if it had been
importante si hubiera quedado
documented no no he was like other
documentado no no él fue como otras
people like people came from New York
personas como vino gente de nueva york
like people came it
como vino gente
's that really
es que de verdad
if you if your
si tu si tu
father or the camera uploads itself if you
padre o de la cámara se sube sola si tú
take it and you every day they are making
coges y tu todos los días están haciendo
content hey and today it's your turn on this subject
contenido oye y hoy te toca este tema
hey what there is you understand wait for
oye lo que hay me entiende esperar a que
you to explode that's where the bad thing is do you
tú explote ahí es donde está en lo malo
understand me be the issue is in the
me entendéis sea el tema está en la
way of doing it in the way of abusing I
manera de hacerlo en la manera de abusar
already told you I uploaded a video today on
ya os digo he subido un vídeo hoy sobre
the subject  on the main channel
el tema en el canal principal
watch it and you will see, it is not that I
mirarlo y así vais a ver no es que yo
am an example of anything or a teacher of anyone
sea ejemplo de nada ni maestro de nadie
but I think it is
pero creo que es la
the correct way to do it
creo que la manera correcta de hacerlo
[Music]
[Música]